showeet.com 2017-08-11

# Privacy policy

At **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** (‘We, ‘Us’), the privacy of our visitors (‘Users’) is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** and how it is used.

When Users navigate on **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** , or download templates, they don’t need to give any personal information. There is no membership system enabled at **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)**.

But, like many other Web sites, **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** makes use of log files and cookies.

**

## Log Files, Cookies and Web Beacons

**

#### Log Files

The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track Users’ movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

**[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** does use cookies to store information about Users’ preferences, record User-specific information on which pages Users access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitor’s browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  1. **Cookies (or browser cookies)** : a cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of User’s computer. Users may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on their browser. However, if Users select this setting they may be unable to access certain parts of **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)**. Unless Users have adjusted their browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when Users direct their browser to **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)**.
  2. **Web Beacons** : pages of **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count Users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).
  3. **DoubleClick DART cookies** : **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on Users’ computer when they are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to Users and their interests (“interest based targeting”). 

DART uses “non-personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about Users, such as their name, email address, physical address, etc.

Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: <http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en>

**

## Google Services (Google Inc.)

**

**[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** uses several services from Google.

Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** , to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

Google uses cookies to help serve the ads it displays on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks.

When the Users visit a partner’s website, a cookie may be dropped on their browser.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to Users based on their visit to **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** and/or other sites on the Internet.

  * Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy: <https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>
  * Users may find out more information by visiting this page on how Google uses data when they use sites or apps on **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** or other websites. See <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>
  * Users may opt-out of personalized advertising by visiting Ads Settings: [https://www.google.com/settings/ads](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/)

**

## Advertising and Commercial affiliation

**

We use third-party advertisements on **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** to support our site.

Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

Our advertising and affiliate partners include Google AdSense (advertising service) and ShareASale (commercial affiliation):

#### Google AdSense (Google Inc.)

Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.

Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout>

  * Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.
  * Place of processing: US – **[Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)** – **[Opt Out](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads)**

#### Commercial affiliation

This type of services allows **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** to display advertisements for third-party products or services. Ads can be displayed either as advertising links or as banners using various kinds of graphics.

Clicks on the icon or banner posted on **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** are tracked by the third-party services listed below, and are shared with **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)**.

For details of which data are collected, please refer to the privacy policy of each service.

##### ShareASale (ShareASale.com Inc.)

ShareAsale is a banner commercial affiliation service provided by ShareAsale.com Inc.

    * Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.
    * Place of processing: US – **[Privacy Policy](http://www.shareasale.com/PrivacyPolicy.pdf)** (pdf document)

**

## Links to third-party websites

**

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)**.

**[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** may contains hyperlinks to other web sites or content or resources.

**[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

When Users click on links and/or ad banners that take you to third-party web sites, they will be subject to the third parties’ privacy policies. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties or for their privacy practices. We encourage Users to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.

Users acknowledge and agree that We are not liable for any loss or damage which may be incurred by Users as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources, or as a result of any reliance placed by Users on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, products or other materials on, or available from, such websites or resources.

**

## Analytics

**

The services contained in this section enable us to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

#### Google Analytics (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** , to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

  * Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.
  * Place of processing: US – **[Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)** – **[Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)**

#### Display advertising extension for Google Analytics (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics on **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** might use Google’s Interest-based advertising, third-party audience data and information from the DoubleClick Cookie to extend analytics with demographics, interests and ads interaction data.

  * Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.
  * Place of processing: US – **[Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/policies/privacy/)** – **[Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)**

#### Google Analytics with anonymized IP (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** , to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

This integration of Google Analytics anonymizes your IP address. It works by shortening Users’ IP addresses within member states of the European Union or in other contracting states to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the complete IP address be sent to a Google server and shortened within the US.

  * Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.
  * Place of processing: US – **[Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)** – **[Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)**

**

## RSS feed management

**

This type of services allows **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** to manage RSS feeds and the distribution of our content. Depending on the characteristics of the service used, these services may be used to insert ads within the content and to gather statistics data from them.

#### FeedBurner (Google Inc.)

Feedburner is a service to manage RSS feeds provided by Google Inc. It allows the collection of statistics on what content is consumed and to insert ads in it.  
Users may choose to receive email blog updates via FeedBurner by submitting an email address to the email subscription form. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime and every email delivered will contain an “Unsubscribe” link.

  * Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.
  * Place of processing: US – **[Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)**

**

## Interaction with external social networks and platforms

**

This type of services allow interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)**.

The interaction and information obtained through **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** are always subject to Users’ privacy settings for each social network.

This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

#### Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)

The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.

  * Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.
  * Place of processing: US – **[Data Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)**

#### Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter)

The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter Inc.

  * Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.
  * Place of processing: US – **[Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/privacy)**

#### Google+ +1 button and social widgets (Google Inc.)

The Google+ +1 button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Google+ social network provided by Google Inc.

  * Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.
  * Place of processing: US – **[Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/)**

#### Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets (Pinterest)

The Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Pinterest platform provided by Pinterest Inc.

  * Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.
  * Place of processing: US – **[Privacy Policy](https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy)**

**

## Contacting the User

**

#### Contact form ( **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** )

By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.

  * Personal Data collected: email address, name.

**

## Miscellaneous

**

#### Comment system managed directly ( **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** )

**[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** has its own internal content comment system.

  * Personal Data collected: Cookies, Usage data and username

#### Content commenting

Content commenting services allow Users to make and publish their comments on the contents of **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)**.

Depending on the settings chosen by the Owner, Users may also leave anonymous comments. If there is an email address among the Personal Data provided by the User, it may be used to send notifications of comments on the same content. Users are responsible for the content of their own comments.

#### Offensive or objectionable ads

We don’t have any direct control over each ad that Google displays, but we can block offensive advertisers. If Users encounter an ad that they feel is offensive, contrary to the philosophy of this website, or is otherwise problematic, should contact us and we’ll make sure it doesn’t appear anymore.

#### Hosting and backend infrastructure

This type of services has the purpose of hosting data and files that enable **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** to run and be distributed as well as to provide a ready-made infrastructure to run specific features or parts of **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)**. Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored.

##### Amazon Web Services (Amazon.com Inc.)

Amazon Web Services is a hosting service provided by Amazon.com Inc.

    * Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

#### SPAM protection

This type of services analyzes the traffic of **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** , potentially containing Users’ Personal Data, with the purpose of filtering it from parts of traffic, messages and content that are recognized as SPAM.

##### Akismet (Automattic Inc.)

Akismet is a SPAM protection service provided by Automattic Inc.

    * Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
    * Place of processing: US – **[Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/)**

**

## Children under the age of 13

**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**

## Changes to Privacy Policy

**

This Privacy Policy may be updated* from time to time for any reason. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

**

## Your consent

**

By using **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** Users consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**

## Definitions

**

#### User

The individual using **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** , which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refers.

#### Data Subject

The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.

#### Personal Data (or Data)

Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.

#### Usage Data

Information collected automatically from **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** (or third party services employed in **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** ), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** , the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** ) and the details about the path followed within **[Showeet.com](http://www.showeet.com/)** with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment.

**

## Contact us

**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please **[contact us](http://www.showeet.com/contact-us/)**.

* * *

*Privacy policy updated and effective: March 14, 2017
